Mary?
Hi.
Hello.
I'm Susan Thompson, resource manager.
Hi, I'm Mary Hansen and I'm applying for one of your kitchen jobs.
Great.
Here's a copy of my resume.
Have a seat, Mary.
Thank you.
Mary, do you have any experience working in the kitchen?
No, but I want to learn.
I work hard and I cook a lot at home.
Okay, well, tell me about yourself.
Well, I love to learn new things.
I'm very organized and I follow directions exactly.
That's why my boss at my last job made me a trainer.
And the company actually gave me a special certificate for coming to work on time every
day for a year.
And I'm taking an english class to improve my writing skills.
That's great.
Why did you leave your last job?
It was graveyard and I need to work days.
Oh, I see.
Well, what hours can you work from 08:00 a.m.
Until 05:00 p.m..
Okay.
Well, do you have any questions for me, Mary?
Yes.
What kind of training is needed?
Not a lot.
Most new workers can learn everything the first day.
Do you have any other questions?
No, I don't think so.
But I've heard a lot of good things about your company and I would really like to work
here.
Well, I have a few more interviews to do today but I will call you tomorrow if you get
the job.
Okay.
It was sure nice to meet you.
Nice meeting you too.
Thank you so much for your time.
Yes, good luck.
Thank you.
Bye.